

# JHONNY IRIARTE

### Software Engineer

Yes, I'm Jhonny Iriarte Condori, a 29 year old full-stack developer with experience in React, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Node.js and Linux server administration. I am characterized by my dynamism, joy and perseverance. My passion for learning and facing technical challenges drives me constantly. I am excited to bring my energy and skills to collaborative teams and take advantage of new opportunities.

## **Education**

• Software Engineer

Academio Full-Stack Web Development and Computer Science Course

2022-2023

Financial Engineering

Diploma in Banking and Financial Risks

2014-2021

 Telecommunications Technician

2008-2011

## **Skills**

- Organization
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Meeting deadlines
- Critical thinking

## Contacto

+591 74320607



iriarte.condori.jhonny25@gmail.com



jhonny-iriarte-condori.netlify.app



Bolivia, Cochabamba, Tiquipaya

## **Experience**

### Academio

Sep 2022 - ago 2023

I have a strong background in developing projects using React.js, JavaScript, Node.js, CSS, and PostgreSQL. My expertise includes creating dynamic and responsive web applications, leveraging efficient database management, and ensuring seamless user experiences.

#### Nerds OnSite

Dic 2019 - ago 2023

Deployment and Management of Digital Services on Linux Servers

II worked as an independent contractor in the deployment, implementation, and management of the Zabbix business model as a monitoring system for pfSense devices, ensuring its efficiency and adaptation to the client's needs

#### SALCEDO PRO

Dic 2018 - ago 2019

Social media management

As an independent contractor, I played a pivotal role in content creation and management on social media platforms. I also contributed to the strategic framework, offering ideas that propelled its development and expansion.

### Digital NetWork.srl

Dic 2011 - Ago 2022

Operational Technician in Structured Cabling.

I specialize in structured wiring, cabinet assembly, and network connectivity, ensuring efficient and reliable telecommunications solutions.

## Languages

• Quechua (Nativo) • Ingles (Intermedio) • Español (Avanzado)

# Software management.

- Node.js CSS
- zabbix Pfsense

- HTML
- Postgres SQL Linux
- Taildwind
- Javascript
- Githup